<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name ="myArray">
        <item>Hey! There</item>
        <item>This app has been exclusively crafted for you</item>
        <item>The best thing about our college is....Uh Sorry</item>
        <item>If you want to delete this app. Go on. But yeah don\'t do this infront of me. Unless you want to see me cry.</item>
        <item>You know what a single app can give you the title of developer</item>
        <item>Mistakes are the sole responsibility of my sour luck</item>
        <item>I was happy initially that I am going to an NIT but now everything\'s pretty much clear</item>
        <item>No matter where you go. You are always surrounded by trees. Hamirpur! we need some privacy</item>
        <item>Friend.Umm… I have got some and I bet that you don\'t want them</item>
        <item>Am I the only guy whose dad never lets him stay awake after 10?</item>
        <item>The worst thing about football is that you have to run a lot.</item>
        <item>The best thing about being lazy is…Uh I am not going to reveal it.</item>
        <item>The only thing with which an Engineer can\'t compromise is his sleep.</item>
        <item>Feeling sad?? Try Hot Chelle Rae</item>
        <item>Am I the only one who thinks that the members of 1D are gay?</item>
        <item>An Apple a day keeps the doctors away. But yeah don\'t eat a dozen of them together</item>
        <item>Well! Yeah sorry for my awful English. Hopefully you are not going to kill me</item>
        <item>Any suggestions from you is highly recommended :-)</item>
        <item>Why are they teaching Basic Electronics to CSE? I barely passed that subject.</item>
        <item>I hate those teachers who take their job very seriously.</item>
        <item>75%.....My foot!.</item>
        <item>Well I am not stalking on you. So feel free to write anything.</item>
        <item>Feeling Tensed?? Baby! Welcome to my world.</item>
        <item>Hey! Have you seen Martian?</item>
        <item>Taylor Swift…when are coming with you next album?</item>
        <item>Are you in OnePiece? If you aren\'t then go have a look.</item>
        <item>I dunno Why animes like Inazuma exist?</item>
        <item>The best thing about DeathNote is....Everything.</item>
        <item>Friend- India is really good in producing Comp Engg. We- Ha-ha-ha</item>
        <item>This is my first app so don\'t expect a lot.</item>
        <item>What NITH needs is a McDonalds.</item>
        <item>Director of NITH fired. Duh? like I care.</item>
        <item>Feeling alone? Drop the developer a message. He is like "Mr.Forever Alone"</item>
        <item>Sometimes I feel We should call this NIT Jaipur instead of NITH</item>
        <item>Too-many Strings. Well I have got more in my pocket.</item>
        <item>Any help is supported.</item>
        <item>Hey! why don\'t you join me?. We\'ll work together</item>
        <item>Game of Thrones…Haven\'t seen something like this before.</item>
        <item>Hi! I am Shashwat(Dev). Though I look like a nerd but believe me I am not.</item>
        <item>Ever heard of Chrissy Costanza before?</item>
        <item>Don\'t forget to have a look at the developer info button below.</item>
        <item>If you are really angry with this app. Sorry can\'t help it</item>
        <item>You can set an alarm too.</item>
        <item>It took me 4 days to make this app</item>
        <item>Currently the app on which I am working on is a Music Player.</item>
        <item>Hopefully you are not finding these animations annoying.</item>
        <item>The best thing about Himachali guys is that all of them are very nice.</item>
        <item>Hey! If you are planning to visit Ghaziabad. Then you are on your own.</item>
        <item>Any idea what\'s the full name of L in Deathnote.</item>
        <item>Hey! Do you remember Jhonny Bravo.</item>
        </string-array>
</resources>